GRID
جريد
SEO KANGJUN
SEO KANGJUN
KIM AHJOONG
كيم أجونج
KIM MUYEOL
كيم مويول
KIM SUNGKYUN
كيم سونغكيون
LEE SIYOUNG
لي سيونغ
GRID
جريد
EPISODE 8
الحلقة 8
LABORATORY 1
المختبر 1
Doctor!
طبيب!
Why? Why does this always happen if you live?
لماذا ا؟  لماذا يحدث هذا دائمًا إذا كنت تعيش؟
No! Don't come out!
لا!  لا تخرج!
Siwon.
شيون.
Siwon!
شيون!
No! Siwon!
لا!  شيون!
You! Why...
أنت!  لماذا...
Siwon. It's okay. It's all right.
شيون.  حسنا.  كل شيء على ما يرام.
"D-Panthenol."
"D- بانثينول."
A vitamin?
فيتامين؟
What must I do?
ماذا يجب علي ان افعل؟
What must I do to change the outcome? You know the answer.
ماذا علي أن أفعل لتغيير النتيجة؟  انت تعرف الاجابة.
If I save someone's life, the Grid disappears. And if I try to change that...
إذا أنقذت حياة شخص ما ، تختفي الشبكة.  وإذا حاولت تغيير ذلك ...
- You must know another way. - I don't.
- يجب أن تعرف طريقة أخرى.  - أنا لا.
No, you must know.
لا ، يجب أن تعرف.
- Hey! Careful! - Come down!
- يا!  حذر!  - إهدأ!
I did it because it's the only way I know.
لقد فعلت ذلك لأنها الطريقة الوحيدة التي أعرفها.
So this is it?
إذن هذا هو؟
Don't try to change anything.
لا تحاول تغيير أي شيء.
I teleported many times, but I'm fine.
لقد انتقلت عن بعد عدة مرات ، لكني بخير.
I'm talking about your damaged DNA.
أنا أتحدث عن حمضك النووي التالف.
You're not sick.
أنت لست مريضا.
You're perishing.
أنت تموت.
Thanks to you, I got much better.
شكرا لك ، لقد تحسنت كثيرا.
Does the janitor have to die for you to live?
هل يجب أن يموت البواب لكي تعيش؟
Then what about my father?
ثم ماذا عن والدي؟
No, right?
لا أليس كذلك؟
You just needed an ID for the lab, didn't you?
أنت فقط بحاجة إلى معرف للمختبر ، أليس كذلك؟
That's what I thought.
هذا ما اعتقدته.
RESTROOM UNDER THE TRUCK
RESTROOM تحت الشاحنة
You even burned a man to death before his child's eyes.
حتى أنك أحرقت رجلاً حتى الموت أمام أعين طفله.
Do people in the future have no conscience?
هل الناس في المستقبل ليس لديهم ضمير؟
Don't you feel sorry for the victims?
ألا تشعر بالأسف على الضحايا؟
A lot of people died during the Joseon Dynasty.
مات الكثير من الناس خلال عهد مملكة جوسون.
Is that heartbreaking too?
هل هذا مفجع أيضا؟
What are you waiting for? Go save those people.
ماذا تنتظر؟  اذهب وانقاذ هؤلاء الناس.
Only then can you call yourself conscientious.
عندها فقط يمكنك أن تطلق على نفسك ضميرًا.
You wouldn't have gone this far if it were for the Grid.
لم تكن لتذهب إلى هذا الحد لو كان من أجل الشبكة.
This must be to save your own skin.
يجب أن يكون هذا لإنقاذ بشرتك.
You're going around ruining everything just to save yourself.
أنت تدور حول تدمير كل شيء فقط لإنقاذ نفسك.
You're the one ruining everything.
أنت الشخص الذي يدمر كل شيء.
Stay out of this.
هذا لا يخصك.
Move forward slowly.
تحرك للأمام ببطء.
You're the one ruining everything.
أنت الشخص الذي يدمر كل شيء.
Stay out of this.
هذا لا يخصك.
MAY 18, 1997
18 مايو 1997
LABORATORY 1
المختبر 1
CUSTODIAL ROOM
غرفة الحجز
Why is it different?
لماذا هو مختلف؟
Siwon. Go over there. Hurry.
شيون.  اذهب إلى هناك.  عجل.
Go now!
اذهب الآن!
Dad!
أب!
Get up.
استيقظ.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Mr. Kwon!
سيد كوون!
That's enough.
هذا يكفي.
He won't tell anyone.
لن يخبر أحدا.
Don't hurt him.
لا تؤذيه.
I won't tell anyone. I swear... I won't.
لن أخبر أحدا.  أقسم ... لن أفعل.
I wouldn't be here if it weren't for his help.
لن أكون هنا لولا مساعدته.
It doesn't matter. I can always turn back time.
لا يهم.  يمكنني دائما العودة بالزمن إلى الوراء.
Then no one will know.
ثم لن يعرف أحد.
Until someone comes, he'll be lying here all night long.
حتى يأتي شخص ما ، سيكون مستلقيًا هنا طوال الليل.
- Please contact his family. - I will.
- الرجاء الاتصال بأسرته.  - أنا سوف.
It's not your fault.
انها ليست غلطتك.
What happened to that child too.
ماذا حدث لذلك الطفل ايضا
YEAR 2000
عام 2000
You won't make it home before sunset at that rate.
لن تعود إلى المنزل قبل غروب الشمس بهذا المعدل.
Who, me?
من انا
Yes, you.
نعم انت.
Kwon Saeha.
كوون سيها.
Do you know me?
هل تعرفني؟
Do you not want to go home quickly?
ألا تريد العودة إلى المنزل بسرعة؟
Because your mom drinks all the time?
لأن والدتك تشرب طوال الوقت؟
Who are you, mister?
من أنت يا سيد؟
I'm a friend of your dad's.
أنا صديق والدك.
My dad passed away
توفي والدي
a long time ago.
منذ وقت طويل.
Is that so?
هل هذا صحيح؟
He passed away mysteriously.
وافته المنية في ظروف غامضة.
Mysteriously? How?
في ظروف غامضة؟  كيف؟
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
I heard it was like he got electrocuted.
سمعت أنه كان كما لو أنه تعرض للصعق بالكهرباء.
Who told you that?
من قال لك ذلك؟
I don't know.
لا أعلم.
My uncle.
عمي.
I heard him say that to my mom.
سمعته يقول ذلك لأمي.
Saeha.
Saeha.
Hurry up and go home. I know you want to go to the bathroom.
اسرع واذهب للمنزل  أعلم أنك تريد الذهاب إلى الحمام.
How did you know?
كيف عرفت؟
Go to the bathroom first when you get home. Okay?
اذهب إلى الحمام أولاً عندما تصل إلى المنزل.  تمام؟
You'll be fine.
ستكون بخير.
You'll become a grown-up soon.
ستصبح بالغًا قريبًا.
Let's do...
دعنا نفعل...
everything we want to do then.
كل ما نريد القيام به بعد ذلك.
Your mom loves you.
والدتك تحبك.
She's just...
إنها فقط ...
having a hard time now.
تواجه صعوبة الآن.
So don't hate her so much.
لذا لا تكرهها كثيرًا.
It's a blue light. Go on now.
إنه ضوء أزرق.  استمر الآن.
It's a green light.
إنه ضوء أخضر.
Saeha. You aren't home yet, are you?
صيحة.  أنت لست في المنزل بعد ، أليس كذلك؟
Are you home, Saeha?
هل انت بالمنزل يا صيحة
GREEN SOUL PSYCHIATRY
الطب النفسي للروح الخضراء
DEPRESSION IS A COLD OF THE MIND
الاكتئاب هو برد للعقل
IF YOU DON'T TREAT DEPRESSION, IT COULD CAUSE PSYCHOLOGICAL DISORDERS...
إذا كنت لا تعالج الاكتئاب ، فقد يتسبب ذلك في اضطرابات نفسية ...
I already injected a lot.
لقد قمت بالفعل بحقن الكثير.
- This will be lethal. - Don't do it, Eojin.
- سيكون هذا قاتلا.  - لا تفعل ذلك ، يوجين.
If she gets it back, it's over.
إذا استعادتها ، ينتهي الأمر.
Don't you know what we've sacrificed for...
ألا تعرف ما ضحينا من أجله ...
What a great persuader.
يا له من مقنع عظيم.
Why is that...
لماذا هذا...
Put that down.
ضعها في أسفل.
You went there, didn't you?
ذهبت إلى هناك ، أليس كذلك؟
Was this the only way?
هل كانت هذه هي الطريقة الوحيدة؟
I saw a world without the Grid.
رأيت عالماً بدون الشبكة.
What was it that I saw then?
ماذا كان ذلك الذي رأيته حينها؟
You know what I'm talking about.
أنت تعرف ما أتحدث عنه.
Saebyeok.
Saebyeok.
When did this happen?
متى حصل هذا؟
Did I see it on my own, or did you show it to me?
هل رأيته بمفردي ، أم هل أظهرته لي؟
Answer me.
جاوبنى.
CHAE JONGYI
تشاي جونجي
Damn it. What is it?
عليك اللعنة.  ما هذا؟
Eojin, get out of there now.
يوجين ، اخرج من هناك الآن.
Do you think I want to be in here?
هل تعتقد أنني أريد أن أكون هنا؟
You must get out now. On the door, they set...
يجب أن تخرج الآن.  على الباب ، وضعوا ...
- Jongyi. - Give it back. Who are you to...
- جونغيي.  - أرجعها.  من أنت حتى ...
Back off.
تراجع.
What did she say?
ماذا قالت؟
I'm not sure. She said "on the door" and...
لست واثق.  قالت "على الباب" و ...
Wait.
انتظر.
You stay here.
أنت ابقى هنا.
No, don't do that!
لا ، لا تفعل ذلك!
Hold on!
يتمسك!
JUNG SAEBYEOK NATIONAL POLICE AGENCY
وكالة الشرطة الوطنية JUNG SAEBYEOK
You're Jung Saebyeok, right? According to the DNA analysis results...
أنت جونغ سايبيوك ، صحيح؟  وفقًا لنتائج تحليل الحمض النووي ...
- Be careful. - Oh, I'm sorry.
- كن حذرا.  - انا اسف.
- Are you okay? - Yes, I'm fine.
- هل انت بخير؟  - نعم انا بخير.
Gosh.
يا الهي.
What happened to you?
ما حدث لك؟
WARNING: POSSESSION OF UNREGISTERED EXPLOSIVES, STAND BY AT CURRENT LOCATION
تحذير: حيازة المتفجرات غير المسجلة ، الوقوف في الموقع الحالي
YOU CANNOT TURN OFF YOUR PHONE
لا يمكنك إيقاف تشغيل هاتفك
Saeha. Are you okay?
صيحة.  انت بخير؟
Saeha!
Saeha!
For God's sake.
من أجل الله.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
I don't know. Saeha suddenly...
لا أعلم.  صيحة فجأة ...
What about him?
ماذا عنه؟
It seemed he got into a fight during lunchtime.
يبدو أنه دخل في شجار أثناء وقت الغداء.
Send him to me once he comes back.
أرسله لي بمجرد عودته.
JUNG SAEBYEOK
شاب سايبيوك
Saeha!
Saeha!
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Hey.
يا.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Are you okay?
انت بخير؟
You're okay, right?
أنت بخير ، صحيح؟
You're safe, right?
أنت بأمان ، صحيح؟
Why wouldn't I be okay?
لماذا لا اكون بخير؟
You sound fine.
يبدو أنك بخير.
It's fine then.
لا بأس إذن.
Good.
جيد.
WELL DONE! YOUR SAFETY IS YOUR FAMILY'S HAPPINESS!
أتقنه!  سلامتك هي سعادة عائلتك!
Hand it over.
سلمها.
He won't tell anyone.
لن يخبر أحدا.
VEHICLE REGISTRATION
استمارة المركبة
"Seoul, Dongseong-gu..."
"سيول ، دونغسونغ غو ..."
NAME: KWON SAEHA
الاسم: كوون ساها
"Kwon Saeha."
"كوون سايها".
By the way...
على فكرة...
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Go bring a station worker.
اذهب واحضر عامل المحطة.
Oh, okay.
حسنا.
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
Why does someone else die every time I save someone?
لماذا يموت شخص آخر في كل مرة أنقذ فيها شخصًا ما؟
You have arrived at your destination. Navigation will end.
لقد وصلت إلى وجهتك.  سينتهي التنقل.
Mother.
الأم.
Yes?
نعم؟
What is this? What happened to you?
ما هذا؟  ما حدث لك؟
Did you have an accident?
هل تعرضت لحادث؟
Are you okay, Mom?
هل انت بخير يا امي
I should be asking you. You're bleeding.
يجب أن أسألك.  انت تنزف.
Who did this to you?
من فعل هذا بالنسبة لك؟
Oh, it got on me during an evacuation drill. It's not mine.
أوه ، لقد أصابني أثناء تمرين الإخلاء.  أنها ليست لي.
What kind of drill makes a person look like that? For goodness' sake.
ما نوع التدريبات التي تجعل الشخص يبدو هكذا؟  بحق الله.
And why can't I find the ointment?
ولماذا لا أجد المرهم؟
Did you really not have an accident?
هل حقا لم تتعرض لحادث؟
My car is parked outside. It's fine.
سيارتي متوقفة بالخارج.  لا بأس.
How did you get that scratch on your face?
كيف حصلت على هذا الخدش على وجهك؟
What's the point of giving you a handsome face?
ما الهدف من إعطائك وجهًا وسيمًا؟
2005 THE HERO OF THE WORLD THE LATE DOCTOR KWON SUKEUN
2005 بطل العالم الطبيب المتأخر كوون سوكيون
10TH ANNUAL MEMORIAL CEREMONY FOR THE DEATH OF DOCTOR KWON SUKEUN
الحفل التذكاري السنوي العاشر لوفاة الطبيب كوون سكيون
Did someone at your company do this? Is that why you're home early?
هل قام شخص ما في شركتك بهذا؟  هل هذا هو سبب عودتك للمنزل مبكرًا؟
Who at my company would do this?
من في شركتي سيفعل هذا؟
That viper.
تلك الأفعى.
Who knows what she has done to my precious son?
من يعرف ماذا فعلت لابني الغالي؟
Who's the viper?
من هو الافعى؟
You know this person, don't you?
أنت تعرف هذا الشخص ، أليس كذلك؟
No, I've never seen him before.
لا ، لم أره من قبل.
What's your husband's relationship with him?
ما علاقة زوجك به؟
Any grudge against him?
أي ضغينة ضده؟
Sorry?
آسف؟
"What's your husband's relationship with him?
"ما علاقة زوجك به؟
Any grudge against him?"
أي ضغينة ضده؟ "
They kept asking me those questions.
ظلوا يسألونني هذه الأسئلة.
I've really never seen him before.
أنا حقا لم أره من قبل.
Even though I clearly told them
على الرغم من أنني أخبرتهم بوضوح
that I had never seen that father of a child in the picture before.
لم أرَ والد الطفل في الصورة من قبل.
I later heard that the janitor had died, and I went to his funeral.
سمعت فيما بعد أن البواب قد مات ، وذهبت إلى جنازته.
Because the lab people assumed that my husband had a grudge against him.
لأن العاملين في المختبر افترضوا أن زوجي لديه ضغينة ضده.
And it was on the same day.
وكان في نفس اليوم.
I was afraid
كنت خائفا
that my husband might have killed him.
أن زوجي قد قتله.
CERTIFICATE OF MERIT KWON SUKEUN
شهادة MERIT KWON SUKEUN
I was afraid your dad might have killed a person
كنت أخشى أن والدك قد قتل شخصًا
and killed himself as well.
وقتل نفسه أيضًا.
But I got kicked out as soon as I got there.
لكنني طردت حالما وصلت إلى هناك.
How did the janitor's family recognize you?
كيف تعرفت عليك عائلة البواب؟
The lab people did.
فعل أهل المختبر.
She was there too.
كانت هناك أيضًا.
The lab people and the deputy director
أهل المختبر ونائب المدير
kicked you out of there?
طردك من هناك؟
And watched you too?
وشاهدتك ايضا؟
At first, I thought they were really treating my husband like a hero.
في البداية ، اعتقدت أنهم كانوا يعاملون زوجي حقًا مثل البطل.
And I thought they frequented our house to check in on you and me.
واعتقدت أنهم يترددون على منزلنا للاطمئنان عليك وعلى نفسي.
Regardless of that,
بغض النظر عن ذلك ،
your dad was the one who built the Grid.
كان والدك هو من بنى الشبكة.
Then why did you worry he might have killed himself?
إذن لماذا تخشى أنه ربما يكون قد قتل نفسه؟
I thought it was strange even before your uncle said it was strange.
اعتقدت أنه كان غريبا حتى قبل أن يقول عمك إنه غريب.
He was totally healthy, but dying from overwork?
كان يتمتع بصحة جيدة ، ولكن يموت من الإرهاق؟
How could I not know
كيف لا اعرف
whether he was in condition to collapse from overwork or not?
وهل كان في حالة الانهيار من الإرهاق أم لا؟
Anyway, they're all liars, those snakes.
على أي حال ، كلهم ​​كذابون ، تلك الثعابين.
Don't trust her blindly just because she's your boss.
لا تثق بها بشكل أعمى لمجرد أنها رئيسك في العمل.
Okay.
تمام.
The person you have called is unavailable. You'll be...
الشخص الذي اتصلت به غير متوفر.  سوف تكون...
KWON SAEHA
كوون ساها
- Should I keep calling? - No.
- هل يجب أن أستمر في الاتصال؟  - رقم.
What's with him going AWOL?
ما الذي يحدثه بدون إذن؟
Maybe he fears nothing because he's got connections.
ربما لا يخشى شيئًا لأنه لديه اتصالات.
He's never flaunted his connections though.
ومع ذلك ، لم يتباهى أبدًا بصلاته.
He looks that way to you because you love people
إنه ينظر إليك بهذه الطريقة لأنك تحب الناس
who get jobs through their connections.
الذين يحصلون على وظائف من خلال اتصالاتهم.
But he's like a pillar of the organization.
لكنه مثل أحد أعمدة المنظمة.
You two must not fear anything too.
أنتما الاثنان يجب ألا تخافا أي شيء أيضًا.
It's this way. Please follow me.
هذا هو الطريق.  أرجوك اتبعني.
My goodness. She did say she heard something from here.
رباه.  لقد قالت إنها سمعت شيئًا من هنا.
Why did she come down here alone?
لماذا نزلت هنا وحدها؟
I feel so bad for her. Poor lady.
اشعر بالاسف تجاهها.  الفقيرة سيدة.
- It's this way. - How could this have happened?
- هذا هو الطريق.  - كيف حدث هذا؟
Let's hear it.
لنستمع الى هذا.
Ms. Choi!
السيدة تشوي!
Investigator Jung Saebyeok?
المحقق جونغ سايبيوك؟
This is where Kim Manok was until this morning.
هذا هو المكان الذي كان فيه كيم مانوك حتى صباح اليوم.
I presume that he killed her during his escape.
أفترض أنه قتلها أثناء هروبه.
Escape? Was he locked up?
هرب؟  هل كان محبوسا؟
It seems so.
يبدو كذلك.
It's been pulled up and down recently.
لقد تم سحبه لأعلى ولأسفل مؤخرًا.
What about these food packages?
ماذا عن عبوات الطعام هذه؟
He couldn't have ordered them in then.
لم يكن بإمكانه طلبهم في ذلك الوقت.
I suppose the woman bought them herself.
أفترض أن المرأة اشترتها بنفسها.
Gloves are over there.
القفازات هناك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Then I guess these were left by the Ghost.
ثم أعتقد أن هؤلاء قد تركهم الشبح.
Since the murderer must've been locked up inside the shutters.
منذ القاتل لابد أنه محبوس داخل المصاريع
Then we'll pick them up.
ثم سنلتقطهم.
No, don't touch them.
لا ، لا تلمسهم.
It's under their jurisdiction. Let them.
إنها تحت سلطتهم القضائية.  دعهم.
I don't see any of your colleagues.
لا أرى أيا من زملائك.
Manok was caught on camera getting out of the station, so they're out asking around.
تم التقاط مانوك بالكاميرا وهو يخرج من المحطة ، لذا فهم بالخارج يسألون.
- On the CCTV cameras here? - Yes.
- على كاميرات الدوائر التلفزيونية المغلقة هنا؟  - نعم.
But the woman...
لكن المرأة ...
I have no expectations now.
ليس لدي توقعات الآن.
Hold on. What time was he caught on camera?
يتمسك.  في أي وقت تم التقاطه على الكاميرا؟
- At 10:00 a.m. - That was only a few hours ago.
- الساعة 10:00 صباحًا - كان ذلك قبل ساعات قليلة فقط.
Kim Manok was caught on camera getting out of Gudong Station at ten this morning.
تم التقاط Kim Manok بالكاميرا وهو يخرج من محطة Gudong في العاشرة من صباح هذا اليوم.
Okay. You can do that.
تمام.  تستطيع فعل ذلك.
The police are already searching for him though.
الشرطة تبحث عنه بالفعل رغم ذلك.
What were you doing when the detectives found traces of him?
ماذا كنت تفعل عندما وجد المحققون آثارا له؟
You may move the body now.
يمكنك تحريك الجسم الآن.
Okay, but...
حسنا ولكن...
Honey...
عسل...
My dear wife.
زوجتي العزيزة.
How did you know Kim Manok was here?
كيف عرفت أن كيم مانوك كان هنا؟
- I didn't. - Then?
- لم أكن.  - ثم؟
I had no clue, but I had to catch him.
لم يكن لدي أي دليل ، لكن كان علي أن أمسك به.
So I thought I should start from where he was last seen.
لذلك اعتقدت أنني يجب أن أبدأ من حيث شوهد آخر مرة.
How did you know he was last seen here?
كيف علمت أنه شوهد آخر مرة هنا؟
When the restaurant owner got hurt,
عندما أصيب صاحب المطعم ،
I asked people in the area then as well.
سألت الناس في المنطقة أيضًا.
Bye, then.
إلى اللقاء.
Have you been transferred yet?
هل تم نقلك بعد؟
Mido.
ميدو.
It's today.
انه اليوم.
That's right. It's today.
هذا صحيح.  انه اليوم.
And it also happens to be today that you informed us of what happened here.
ويصادف أيضًا أنك أبلغتنا اليوم بما حدث هنا.
But that doesn't mean your relocation will be canceled.
لكن هذا لا يعني أنه سيتم إلغاء نقلك.
I informed you hoping you would catch the woman soon.
أبلغتك على أمل أن تمسك بالمرأة قريبًا.
Because if she's not caught, it's pointless to catch Kim Manok.
لأنه إذا لم يتم القبض عليها ، فمن غير المجدي الإمساك بكيم مانوك.
I think you would suit us better than the police.
أعتقد أنك ستناسبنا أفضل من الشرطة.
The Secretariat.
السكرتارية.
I hope you'll find out for yourself...
أتمنى أن تكتشف بنفسك ...
what she is capable of doing
ما هي قادرة على القيام به
and what technology she uses.
وما التكنولوجيا التي تستخدمها.
And where it takes human civilization.
وحيث تأخذ الحضارة الإنسانية.
I truly hope that you'll see for yourself.
آمل حقًا أن ترى بنفسك.
- Wait. - Sorry?
- انتظر.  - آسف؟
Please go first. I'll catch up with you.
من فضلك اذهب أولا.  سوف اللحاق بك.
DO NOT CROSS UNDER INVESTIGATION
لا تعبر قيد التحقيق
DR. KWON SUKEUN TO BE AWARDED THE NOBEL PRIZE POSTHUMOUSLY FOR THE FIRST TIME?
الدكتور.  كوون سكيون لحصوله على جائزة نوبل بعد وفاتها للمرة الأولى؟
...HAS ALLEGEDLY BEEN NOMINATED...
... تم ترشيحه حسب الادعاء ...
...CANNOT BE AWARDED POSTHUMOUSLY...
... لا يمكن منحها بعد فوات الأوان ...
...DONE A GREAT SERVICE TO MANKIND...
... أنجزت خدمة عظيمة للبشرية ...
HOW HIS COLLEAGUES REMEMBER THE LATE DR. KWON SUKEUN
كيف يتذكر زملاؤه تاريخ د.  كوون سكيون
HE DIDN'T STAND OUT, BUT HE DEDICATED HIMSELF TO RESEARCHING THE GRID
لم يقف ، لكنه كرس نفسه للبحث في الشبكة
When that woman came to take you,
عندما أتت تلك المرأة لأخذك ،
I should've thrown salt at her and kicked her out.
كان يجب أن ألقي عليها الملح وطردها.
Where did she take me?
إلى أين أخذتني؟
Where else? The Administration Bureau.
اين أيضا؟  ديوان الإدارة.
Talking about special employment...
الحديث عن العمالة الخاصة ...
If Doctor Kwon's son didn't work at the Administration Bureau, then who...
إذا لم يعمل نجل الدكتور كوون في مكتب الإدارة ، فمن ...
Goodness.
صلاح.
Special employment?
عمالة خاصة؟
The founder of the Grid has changed.
لقد تغير مؤسس الشبكة.
Does that mean...
هل هذا يعني...
SONGJE POLICE STATION, JUNG SAEBYEOK
محطة شرطة SONGJE ، JUNG SAEBYEOK
Feel free to contact me if you need anything.
لا تتردد في الاتصال بي إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء.
I should've killed that jerk.
كان يجب أن أقتل هذا الأحمق.
It's this house.
إنه هذا المنزل.
Earlier, for a moment,
في وقت سابق ، للحظة ،
I remembered what we used to be like.
تذكرت ما اعتدنا أن نكون عليه.
Getting calls from you while at work.
تلقي مكالمات منك أثناء العمل.
During lunch breaks.
خلال استراحات الغداء.
Or before getting off work.
أو قبل النزول من العمل.
We talked about whether we'd be home late.
تحدثنا عما إذا كنا سنعود إلى المنزل في وقت متأخر.
Or where we should meet up for dinner. Things like that.
أو حيث يجب أن نلتقي لتناول العشاء.  أشياء من هذا القبيل.
We used to talk about such trivial things.
كنا نتحدث عن أشياء تافهة.
Don't be so offended by it.
لا تنزعج من ذلك.
It was just for a brief moment.
كان فقط للحظة وجيزة.
That's not it.
هذا ليس هو.
Why did you wonder if I was okay?
لماذا تساءلت إذا كنت بخير؟
I just had a bad dream.
لقد حلمت للتو بحلم سيء.
It's not that I dream about you every day though.
ليس الأمر أنني أحلم بك كل يوم.
We'll be late.
سوف نتأخر.
For what?
لماذا؟
Why do you think the Ghost locked him up? She's the one who helped him flee.
لماذا تعتقد أن الشبح حبسه؟  هي التي ساعدته على الفرار.
What I really don't understand is
ما لا أفهمه حقًا هو
why she let him go now.
لماذا تركته يذهب الآن.
She opened the shutters. That means she intended to let him go.
فتحت المصاريع.  هذا يعني أنها تنوي السماح له بالرحيل.
Maybe she knew we'd come to get him.
ربما عرفت أننا سنأتي لنحصل عليه.
How?
كيف؟
I'm sure it's easy for the Ghost to stop him from running away.
أنا متأكد من أنه من السهل على الشبح منعه من الهروب.
Can I take this off?
هل يمكنني خلع هذا؟
You've changed a lot.
لقد تغيرت كثيرًا.
Before, you would have taken it off without even asking.
من قبل ، كنت قد خلعته دون أن تطلب ذلك.
That's not what I meant.
ليس هذا ما قصدته.
Is something wrong with Mr. Kwon Saeha?
هل هناك خطب ما في السيد كوون سيها؟
How do you know him?
كيف تعرفت عليه؟
Is he really sick?
هل هو مريض حقا؟
Is that why he didn't come?
هل لهذا السبب لم يأت؟
How do you know Kwon Saeha?
كيف تعرف كون صيحة؟
Of course I do...
بالطبع افعل...
We met the other day.
التقينا في ذلك اليوم.
He suddenly left this afternoon and didn't come back.
فجأة غادر بعد ظهر اليوم ولم يعد.
- Where are you going now? - What?
- إلى أين أنت ذاهب الآن؟  - ماذا؟
- Why? - What do you mean?
- لماذا؟  - ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
I mean, why do you ask where I'm going?
اعني لماذا تسأل اين انا ذاهب؟
Can't I ask?
لا استطيع ان اسال؟
Yes, you can.
نعم تستطيع.
I should get back to the station.
يجب أن أعود إلى المحطة.
Songje Station.
محطة Songje.
Okay, then.
حسنا إذا.
Thanks for the ride.
شكرا على الجولة.
That's not the way to the station.
هذا ليس الطريق إلى المحطة.
CALLING KWON SAEHA
داعيا كوون ساها
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
- Who are you people? - Hey, don't do that.
- من انتم ايها الناس؟  - مهلا ، لا تفعل ذلك.
Damn it.
عليك اللعنة.
Gosh, what's their problem?
يا إلهي ، ما هي مشكلتهم؟
- Not here? - No, sir.
- ليس هنا؟  - لا سيدي.